A Guide to the Lilla Richards Collection, 1914-2016 (bulk 1970-2001)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 9: Organizations Files, 1973-2016
  - Lilla Richards' Files on Organizations - Vocational Education Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Series 10: Dranesville District Supervisor Correspondence, 1988-1991
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1988, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1989 (Part 1), 1989 January-May (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1989 (Part 2), 1989 June-August (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1989 (Part 3), 1989 September-October (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1989 (Part 4), 1989 November-December (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 1), 1990 January-February (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 2), 1990 March (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 3), 1990 March-April (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 4), 1990 May-July (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 5), 1990 August (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 6), 1990 September-October (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1990 (Part 7), 1990 November-December (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1991 (Part 1), 1991 January-February (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1991 (Part 2), 1991 March-May (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1991 (Part 3), 1991 June-August (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1991 (Part 4), 1991 September-October (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor, 1991 (Part 5), 1991 November-December (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Lilla Richards' Correspondence as Dranesville District Supervisor - No Date, Undated (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Series 11: McCloud Brandon Hodges, Jr Scrapbooks on Arlington and Fairfax Counties, 1958-1969
  - McCloud Brandon Hodges, Jr., Arlington, Va., Scrapbook 1 of newspaper clippings on Arlington and Fairfax County development issues, land use, taxation, planning, transportation, roads, etc., 1958-1965 (Box 90)
  - McCloud Brandon Hodges, Jr., Arlington, Va., Scrapbook 2 of newspaper clippings on Arlington and Fairfax County development issues, land use, taxation, planning, transportation, roads, etc., 1966 (Box 90)
  - McCloud Brandon Hodges, Jr., Arlington, Va., Scrapbook 3 of newspaper clippings on Arlington and Fairfax County development issues, land use, taxation, planning, transportation, roads, etc., 1967-1969 (Box 91)
- Series 12: Poster Boards, 1980-1997
  - Lilla Richards Poster Boards of newspaper clippings and original photographs on Fairfax County development, planning, transportation, roads, politics, elections, land use, taxation, etc., 1980-1985 (Drawer OV Drawer)
  - Lilla Richards Poster Boards of newspaper clippings and original photographs on Fairfax County development, planning, transportation, roads, politics, elections, land use, taxation, etc., 1986-1987 (Drawer OV Drawer)
  - Lilla Richards Poster Boards of newspaper clippings and original photographs on Fairfax County development, planning, transportation, roads, politics, elections, land use, taxation, etc., 1988-1990 (Drawer OV Drawer)
  - Lilla Richards Poster Boards of newspaper clippings and original photographs on Fairfax County development, planning, transportation, roads, politics, elections, land use, taxation, etc., 1992, 1997 (Drawer OV Drawer)